In this final lesson, you'll use GitHub to provide to generate clean and professional documentation
for this project.
Normal is a kind of documentation placed in red meat.md file in this file, but since
that file I will use to guide you and other students how to work with this repository where
I will store the source code, how to use the source code examples, it will be busy, and
feel create documentation in separate file which we call documentation.md.
So, documentation.md file will include the information about short overview of the application,
its main features, the technical stack, some set up instructions, and of course some usage
guide how to work with application.
But then of this lesson, you will have complete project documentation, ready for developers
to read and reference.
Okay let's start creating, I have prepared a prompt, I will close this red meat file,
so generate developer documentation for this project and save it as documentation.md.
In the wrap route, include a short project overview, key features, technical stacks, type
instruction, as commands for install, for arm, for built-in for test, and add some
usage guide with basic steps.
So we can start, but before, normally a I can add some sections which we don't list
here, and if you'd like to specify, add only sections with listed here, no any other sections
you need to clearly write it, don't add any other sections, yes, not listed here.
So when any other need for instruction, then just this sections we mentioned.
Okay let's wait, you see he's used a planning, recommendation, products, let's wait a bit.
I've even created some to those for documentation, so create the documentation, file, verify,
file, let me change this, okay, so we have the documentation ready, we have the project
overview, a small calculator up with these technologies which can implement, implement simple,
file, stop, calculate the UI, blah, blah, blah, we here release the key features, then
we release the technical stack, we use, we have some setup instructions, how to install dependencies,
how to run the project, how to build it for production, and how to run the test.
We also have usage guide on basic steps, so how to start with this application.
And I guess that's all, I would like to show you in this lesson, I hope it was useful,
and see you in the next lessons.